[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "How do you actually pronounce your name?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "actually", "pronounce", "your", "name", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "Charlize Theron.", "answer_tokens": ["Charlize", "Theron", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "What is the correct South African, dare I say it, African way of pronouncing this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "correct", "South", "African", ",", "dare", "I", "say", "it", ",", "African", "way", "of", "pronouncing", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Charlize Theron.", "answer_tokens": ["Charlize", "Theron", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "And you quite consciously went and taught yourself how to speak in an American accent, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "quite", "consciously", "went", "and", "taught", "yourself", "how", "to", "speak", "in", "an", "American", "accent", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "Do you speak African certainly?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "speak", "African", "certainly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Every day.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Can you speak African to her?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "speak", "African", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "So you speak it completely fluently?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "speak", "it", "completely", "fluently", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Oh, I think more fluently than I speak English.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "more", "fluently", "than", "I", "speak", "English", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Woody?", "question_tokens": ["Woody", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Guilty as charged?", "question_tokens": ["Guilty", "as", "charged", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "None of this -- there's no truth to it whatsoever.", "answer_tokens": ["None", "of", "this", "--", "there", "'s", "no", "truth", "to", "it", "whatsoever", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "But he calls you Chuck?", "question_tokens": ["But", "he", "calls", "you", "Chuck", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Heading that way?", "question_tokens": ["Heading", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Because I want to actually work until I'm 108, and I don't think you can't have longevity if you just kind of fall back on one aspect of what you are.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "want", "to", "actually", "work", "until", "I", "'m", "108", ",", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "ca", "n't", "have", "longevity", "if", "you", "just", "kind", "of", "fall", "back", "on", "one", "aspect", "of", "what", "you", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "There's never the safe one, is there?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "never", "the", "safe", "one", ",", "is", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CD", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, I don't think human beings are -- I think we're pretty complicated.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "human", "beings", "are", "--", "I", "think", "we", "'re", "pretty", "complicated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Oh, dear God, what is this an hour show?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "dear", "God", ",", "what", "is", "this", "an", "hour", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Yes, we got plenty of time, seriously.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "got", "plenty", "of", "time", ",", "seriously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "Do you really love the aging process?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "really", "love", "the", "aging", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "So far, I said.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "far", ",", "I", "said", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "Is that because it's obviously treating you quite well?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "because", "it", "'s", "obviously", "treating", "you", "quite", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Look, I'm only 35.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "'m", "only", "35", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "So you get to these random houses, and what do you do?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "get", "to", "these", "random", "houses", ",", "and", "what", "do", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I -- the first thing I do is I inspect every closet and drawer.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "the", "first", "thing", "I", "do", "is", "I", "inspect", "every", "closet", "and", "drawer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "There are guys going to say who is this weirdo?", "question_tokens": ["There", "are", "guys", "going", "to", "say", "who", "is", "this", "weirdo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "It's fascinating watching you because I know you don't like watching yourself, do you?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "fascinating", "watching", "you", "because", "I", "know", "you", "do", "n't", "like", "watching", "yourself", ",", "do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "I've gotten a lot better.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "gotten", "a", "lot", "better", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Do you know how much money you've taken at the box office in movies you've been in?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "much", "money", "you", "'ve", "taken", "at", "the", "box", "office", "in", "movies", "you", "'ve", "been", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "God, no.", "answer_tokens": ["God", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "That's not bad, is it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "not", "bad", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "That sounds good.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "sounds", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "You don't care how much they make, these films?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "care", "how", "much", "they", "make", ",", "these", "films", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I care.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billion dollars"]}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "Which one would you prefer at this stage of your career?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "would", "you", "prefer", "at", "this", "stage", "of", "your", "career", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "I guess I would take the one that makes the billion dollars, but the critics don't care for it because then I can go make seven of the ones that I love.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", "I", "would", "take", "the", "one", "that", "makes", "the", "billion", "dollars", ",", "but", "the", "critics", "do", "n't", "care", "for", "it", "because", "then", "I", "can", "go", "make", "seven", "of", "the", "ones", "that", "I", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Hey, Todd, do we even have factory work?", "question_tokens": ["Hey", ",", "Todd", ",", "do", "we", "even", "have", "factory", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I'm sorry.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sorry", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Todd"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "I mean, when you look back on it now, obviously brilliant for you in your career, but to actually play that role, what was the experience like?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "when", "you", "look", "back", "on", "it", "now", ",", "obviously", "brilliant", "for", "you", "in", "your", "career", ",", "but", "to", "actually", "play", "that", "role", ",", "what", "was", "the", "experience", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "That was the greatest gift I think I've ever been given in my career.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "the", "greatest", "gift", "I", "think", "I", "'ve", "ever", "been", "given", "in", "my", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Academy Award"]}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Yes, look, it's absolutely amazing to win an Academy Award.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "look", ",", "it", "'s", "absolutely", "amazing", "to", "win", "an", "Academy", "Award", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Did you watch the Oscars as a young girl?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "watch", "the", "Oscars", "as", "a", "young", "girl", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "I did, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Have you met him?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "met", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Academy Award"]}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "When did you meet him?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "you", "meet", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "The first time I met him, I had just won the Academy Award.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "first", "time", "I", "met", "him", ",", "I", "had", "just", "won", "the", "Academy", "Award", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "And what did he say to you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "he", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "The nicest things that any icon or hero could possibly say to you.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "nicest", "things", "that", "any", "icon", "or", "hero", "could", "possibly", "say", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nelson Mandela"], "LOCATION": ["South Africa"]}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Like what?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Just, you know, giving me credit for being a South African and kind of putting South Africa on the map, which I didn't, but I'll take that any day from Nelson Mandela.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", ",", "you", "know", ",", "giving", "me", "credit", "for", "being", "a", "South", "African", "and", "kind", "of", "putting", "South", "Africa", "on", "the", "map", ",", "which", "I", "did", "n't", ",", "but", "I", "'ll", "take", "that", "any", "day", "from", "Nelson", "Mandela", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Any other?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Women?", "question_tokens": ["Women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Africans"]}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Who else?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "I don't know if they were women but I know another category South Africans have won.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "they", "were", "women", "but", "I", "know", "another", "category", "South", "Africans", "have", "won", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "How much of it is down to what happened, if anything?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "it", "is", "down", "to", "what", "happened", ",", "if", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Look, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Does it haunt you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "haunt", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "No, it doesn't haunt me.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "haunt", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "But, there must be things that you got from your father?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "there", "must", "be", "things", "that", "you", "got", "from", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "He was a -- he was a fun guy.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "a", "--", "he", "was", "a", "fun", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "And what can be done to tackle it properly do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "can", "be", "done", "to", "tackle", "it", "properly", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "HERON: I think it's a lack of education.", "answer_tokens": ["HERON", ":", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "lack", "of", "education", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "How can you get them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "can", "you", "get", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "You can go to our web site, CharlizeAfricaOutreach.org.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "go", "to", "our", "web", "site", ",", "CharlizeAfricaOutreach.org", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "NNS", ",", "RB", ":", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "And directly help?", "question_tokens": ["And", "directly", "help", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "And -- yes, directly -- look, here's the thing.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "--", "yes", ",", "directly", "--", "look", ",", "here", "'s", "the", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Is that the problem?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "problem", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "It's been -- it's knowledge.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "--", "it", "'s", "knowledge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "I'll explain why.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "explain", "why", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "What issues in America wind you up?", "question_tokens": ["What", "issues", "in", "America", "wind", "you", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "There are a few.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "are", "a", "few", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "Do you still feel with Obama that he is capable of being as great as everybody hoped?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "feel", "with", "Obama", "that", "he", "is", "capable", "of", "being", "as", "great", "as", "everybody", "hoped", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "Yes, I think he's incredibly capable of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "incredibly", "capable", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Do you think you'll never get married?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "'ll", "never", "get", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I -- I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "What do you want?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "want", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "You know this was never about the gold.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "this", "was", "never", "about", "the", "gold", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "That is so -- no -- a few.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "so", "--", "no", "--", "a", "few", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "How many fingers?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "fingers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "No, a few.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "a", "few", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Why was that, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "that", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "You know, I really love my job and I love my fans, but when it comes to my relationships, it's something that I keep very sacred to me, it's very private.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "really", "love", "my", "job", "and", "I", "love", "my", "fans", ",", "but", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "my", "relationships", ",", "it", "'s", "something", "that", "I", "keep", "very", "sacred", "to", "me", ",", "it", "'s", "very", "private", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Am I allowed to pry?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "allowed", "to", "pry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "No, and after --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "and", "after", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 608, "question": "If you ate that taco?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "ate", "that", "taco", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "-- if they had images of you spoon-feeding this --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "if", "they", "had", "images", "of", "you", "spoon-feeding", "this", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Yes, I mean, it was just such an innocent introduction.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "it", "was", "just", "such", "an", "innocent", "introduction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Any -- any truth to that?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "--", "any", "truth", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "This is the problem when you're single and your friends kind of come out to help you and, you know, take you out for a nice meal and --", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "problem", "when", "you", "'re", "single", "and", "your", "friends", "kind", "of", "come", "out", "to", "help", "you", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "take", "you", "out", "for", "a", "nice", "meal", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Keanu"]}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 651, "question": "Not a sliver of truth?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "a", "sliver", "of", "truth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 652, "answer": "No, I've known Keanu for over 15 years.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'ve", "known", "Keanu", "for", "over", "15", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Aren't you married?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "n't", "you", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "I'm not trying to pull you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "trying", "to", "pull", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]